Schein, Donald; Papers apap209
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 May (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 June (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 July (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 August (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 September (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 October (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 November (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 December (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1979, Endowment Committee (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1979, Financial Statements (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1979, Journal (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1979, MHCET Financial Statement (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1979, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1979, The Nixon Administration Public Broadcasting Papers: A Summary, NAEB Publication (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1979, Notes (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1979, NYS Public Television Survey (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1979, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, & Miller (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1979, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1979, Public Broadcasting (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32-34)
- 1979, Public Telecommunications Review (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1979, Reports and Publications on Public Broadcasting (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1979, Revision of By-Laws (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1979, Schein Family Photos (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1979, Security (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1979, State Education Department Capital Grants, 1979-1985 (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1979, WMHT Internal Records (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1979, WMHT Internal Records (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1979, WMHT Personal Policy Manual (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2-3)
- 1979, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4-5)
- 1980, Access, Periodical (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1980, Association for Public Broadcasting (APB) (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1980, Bromberg, Ellis (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1980, Budget and Finance Committee (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1980, Community Advisory Board, 1980-1987 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1980, Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1980-1987 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-12)
- 1980, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Computing and Telecommunication Planning Task Force Final Report (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1980, CPB Meeting, 1980 July 15 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1980, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1980, CPB Publications (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16-17)
- 1980, Current, Periodical (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 January (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 February (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 March (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 April (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 May (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 June (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 July (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 August (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 September (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 October (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 November (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 December (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1980, Development Committee (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1980, Endowment Committee (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1980, Equipment File, 1980-1985 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1980, Equipment File, 1980-1985 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1980, Equipment File, Clippings and Vendor Publications, 1980-1985 (Box 15 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1980, Inside Albany, Series, 1980-1986 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-2)
- 1980, I Love New York, Series, 1980-1986 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1980, Journal (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1980, Keeping P.A.C.E with the New Television (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1980, London Trip (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1980, Long-Range Planning Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1980, MHCET Financial Statement (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1980, NEH Grant Applications (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1980, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1980, Notes on Board Meetings (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1980, NPR Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1980, "NPR or Not? Membership Options", Address (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1980, PBS Information Binder (?) (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1980, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, & Miller (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1980, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1980, PBS Merit Awards (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1980, Public Broadcasting (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18-24)
- 1980, Public Broadcasting News, Periodical, 1980 November (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1980, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1980, Public Telecommunications Review (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1980, Russell Sage Conference, 1980 October 17 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1980, Staff Memoranda, 1980-1986 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1980, Spector, Beryl (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1980, Television Quarterly, Periodical, Fall 1980 (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1980, van Rijsewijk, Derk (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1980, WMHT Internal Records (Box 16 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33-40)
- 1980, WMHT Internal Records, 1980-1983 (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1980, WMHT Procedure Manual (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1980, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3-4)
- 1980, WMHT Ratings and Surveys, 1980-1987 (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5-6)
- 1981, Access, Periodical (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1981, Capital Expense Meeting (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1981, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Five-Year Plan (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1981, CPB Publications (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1981, CPB Reports (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1981, Current, Periodical (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 January (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 February (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 March (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 April (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 May (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 June (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 July (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 August (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 September (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 October (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 November (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 December (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1981, Educational and Industrial Television (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1981, Endowment Committee (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1981, Enhancing Interviewing Skills of Income Maintenance Workers: A Training Manual, SUNY Albany Publication (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1981, Grimmer, Jean (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1981, The Humanist, Periodical, 1981 September-1981 October (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1981, Instructional Television Fixes Service (ITFS), 1981-1984 (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1981, The MacNeil/Lehrer Report Broadcast Review and Index (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1981, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1981, PBS Underwriting Guidelines (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1981, Public Broadcasting (Box 17 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34-35)
- 1981, Public Broadcasting (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-6)
- 1981, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1981, Reaction Line Transcripts, 1981-1986 (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1981, School of Broadcasting (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1981, WAMC, 1981-1986 (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1981, WARM Application (?) (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1981, What Broadcasters Should Know About Satellites, Technical Publication (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1981, WMHT Development Department (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1981, WMHT Internal Records (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14-22)
- 1981, The WMHT Program Guide, Program (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23-24)
- 1981, WMHT Salary Rates, 1981-1986 (Box 18 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1982, Access (Periodical) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1982, Advertising, 1982-1985 (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1982, Arbitron Radio Market Reports Description of Methodology (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1982, Broadcasting (Periodical) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1982, Building Construction (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1982, Buying or Building a Broadcast Station (National Association of Broadcasters Report) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1982, Channels of Communication (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1982, Current (Periodical) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1982, Daily Calendar, 1982 November-1983 June (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 January (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 February (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 March (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1982, Day-Timer (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 May (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 June (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 July (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 August (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 September (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 October (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 November (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 December (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1982, Educational and Industrial Television (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1982, Endowment Committee (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1982, The Independent Film & Video Monthly (Periodical) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1982, Journal (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1982, Mid-Hudson Transmitter (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1982, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1982, Notebook (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1982, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1982, PBS National Narrowcast Service, 1982-1984 (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1982, PBS Underwriting Guidelines (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1982, Prospects Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1982, PBS Legal Memoranda (Schwartz, Woods and Miller) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1982, Public Broadcasting (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34-38)
- 1982, Public Broadcasting news (Periodical), 1982 April (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1982, The Public Broadcasting Report (periodical) (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1982, Schenectady Economic Development Advisory Board, 1982-1984 (Box 19 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1982, Schenectady Economic Development Advisory Board, 1982-1984 (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1982, Shayne, Alan (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1982, Staff Registrations (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1982, WMHT Internal Records (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4-8)
- 1982, WMHT-FM Internal Records, 1982-1985 (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1982, WMHT Personnel Committee (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10-11)
- 1982, WMHT Personnel Policy Revisions (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1982, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13-16)
- 1983, Channels of Communication (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1983, CPB Development Newsletter (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1983, CPB Publications (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1983, Current (periodical) (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1983, Daily Calendar, 07/1983-12/1983 (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 January (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 February (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 March (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 April (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 May (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 June (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 July (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 August (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 September (Box 20 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 October (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 November (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1983, day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 December (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1983, Endowment Committee (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1983, Exit Interviews, 1983-1986 (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1983, Finance Committee (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1983, Journal (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1983, Management (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1983, Mexico Trip (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1983, Mid-Hudson FM Transmitter, 1983-1987 (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10-11)
- 1983, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1983, PBS Annual Meeting (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1983, PBS FY1984 Planning Budget (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1983, PBS Legal Memoranda (Schwartz, Woods and Miller) (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1983, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1983, Public Broadcasting (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-24)
- 1983, The Public Broadcasting Report (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1983, RISE Fifth Anniversary Celebration Program (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1983, Schenectady County Grants, 1983-1986 (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1983. Schwartz, Woods & Miller, 1983-1987 (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1983, Smoking (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1983, State Education Department, 1983-1986 (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1983, WMHT [Program] (Box 21 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1983, WMHT [Program] (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-2)
- 1983, WMHT Finance Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1983, WMHT Internal Records (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4-11)
- 1984, Auction Promotional Poster (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1984, Channels of Communication (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1984, Communications Director Search (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1984, Corporate Support, 1984-1986 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1984, County Funding for WMHT (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1984, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Seminar: "Management Techniques for Chief Executive Officers" (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1984, CPB Marketing Seminar (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1984, Current (Periodical) (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1984, Daily Calendar, 01/1984-06/1984 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 January (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 February (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 March (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 April (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 May (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 June (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 July (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 August (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 September (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 October (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 November (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 December (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1984, EITV (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1984, Endowment Committee (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1984, Engineering Department (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1984, Facilities Guidelines For Public Television Stations, PBS Engineering Report (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1984, Federighi, Renie, 1984-1987 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1984, Glens Falls Translator, 1984-1986 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1984, Grant Writing Seminar (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1984, Instructional Television Fixed Services (ITFS), 1984-1987 (Box 22 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1984, Johnson, Karen, Mayor of Schenectady (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1984, Journal (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1984, Management (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1984, National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant Applications (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1984, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1984, Nominating Committee (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1984, Nuveen Fund Prospectus (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7-8)
- 1984, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, and Miller (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1984, PBS Managers' Meeting (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1984, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1984, Personnel Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting (Box 23 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13-25)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting News, Periodical, 1984 May (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1984, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1984, Public Television and Radio and State Governments (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1984, Satellite Uplink, 1984-1986 (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5-6)
- 1984, State Education Department, 1984-1986 (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1984, Station Histories (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1984, The Teleport Concept, Bound Report on Broadcasting in Erie County (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1984, Union, 1984-1986 (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10-12)
- 1984, VBI Data Delivery Service, 1984-1985 (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1984, Westerly (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1984, WLIW, 1984-1985 (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1984, WMHT, Program (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16-17)
- 1984, WMHT Channels, Internal Newsletter (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records (Box 24 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19-26)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-6)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records, 1984-1987 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1984, WMHT-FM Internal Records, 1984-1986 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1984, WMHT Trustees Manual (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1984, WUSV Contract (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10-11)
- 1984, WUSV Purchase, 1984-1987 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12-13)
- 1985, Albany County Grant, 1985-1986 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1985, Albany Tricentennial (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1985, Baruch, Ralph M. (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1985, Board Directories, 1985-1992 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1985, Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18-19)
- 1985, Capital District Magazine Proposal (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1985, Carriage of Public Television By Cable Systems (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1985, Channels of Communications (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1985, Correspondence (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1985, Current (Periodical) (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1985, Daily Calendar, 1985 July-1985 December (Box 25 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)